<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Car Recommendations</string>
    <string name="app_intro">We will help find car recommendations for you.  Enter car brand:</string>
    <string name="pilih_tipe">Select car type:</string>
    <string name="merek_mobil">Brand (Toyota or Daihatsu)</string>
    <string name="mobil_manual">Manuals</string>
    <string name="mobil_matic">Matic</string>
    <string name="lihat_rekomendasi">View Recommendations</string>
    <string name="tentang_aplikasi">About Application</string>
    <string name="copyright">This application was created to make it easier for users who are searching         car recommendations. The application will display several relevant car recommendations based on         input the brand and type of car (manual or automatic) that has been entered by         user.  Copyright © 2024 Giyats Almanfalutti. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
    <string name="toyota_matic">RECOMMENDATIONS FOR TOYOTA AUTOMATIC CARS</string>
    <string name="isi_toyota_matic">1. Toyota Avanza The Toyota Avanza is a 7-seater MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its affordable price, fuel economy and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car at an affordable price, able to accommodate many passengers, and comfortable for long trips. Specification: Engine: 1.3L 4 cylinder and 1.5L 4 cylinder Power: 98 PS (1.3L) and 106 PS (1.5L) Torque: 12.4 Nm (1.3L) and 14.1 Nm (1.5L) Transmission: 5-speed manual and CVT automatic Fuel consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake   2. Toyota Kijang Innova The Toyota Kijang Innova is a 7-seater MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its elegant design, reliable performance and comfortable interior. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance and a spacious cabin. Specification: Engine: 2.0L 4 cylinder and 2.4L 4 cylinder Power: 139 PS (2.0L) and 149 PS (2.4L) Torque: 183 Nm (2.0L) and 239 Nm (2.4L) Transmission: 5-speed manual and 6-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 10-12 km/liter (in city) and 13-15 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist, panoramic sunroof  3. Toyota Fortuner The Toyota Fortuner is a 7-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle) which is famous for its dashing design, reliable performance and complete features. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance and sophisticated features. Specification: Engine: 2.4L 4 cylinder and 2.8L 4 cylinder Power: 149 PS (2.4L) and 204 PS (2.8L) Torque: 400 Nm (2.4L) and 420 Nm (2.8L) Transmission: 6-speed manual and 6-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 9-11 km/liter (in city) and 12-14 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist, adaptive cruise control, lane departure warning, forward collision warning</string>
    <string name="toyota_manual">TOYOTA MANUAL CAR RECOMMENDATIONS</string>
    <string name="isi_toyota_manual">1. Toyota Corolla The Toyota Corolla is a sedan that is famous for its elegant design, reliable performance and comfortable interior. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance and a spacious cabin. Specification: Engine: 1.8L 4 cylinder Power: 140 PS Torque: 171 Nm Transmission: 6-speed manual or CVT automatic Fuel consumption: 12-14 km/liter (in city) and 15-17 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist   2. Toyota Yaris The Toyota Yaris is a hatchback car that is famous for its sporty design, reliable performance and complete features. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car with a contemporary design, strong performance and sophisticated features. Specification: Engine: 1.5L 4 cylinder Power: 107 PS Torque: 140 Nm Transmission: 5-speed manual or CVT automatic Fuel consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist, paddle shift   3. Toyota Rush Toyota Rush is a 7-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle) which is famous for its sporty design, reliable performance and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance, and a cabin that can accommodate many passengers. Specification: Engine: 1.5L 4 cylinder Power: 104 PS Torque: 138 Nm Transmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 10-12 km/liter (in city) and 13-15 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist</string>
    <string name="daihatsu_matic">DAIHATSU MATIC CAR RECOMMENDATIONS</string>
    <string name="isi_daihatsu_matic">1. Daihatsu Ayla Type D AT Daihatsu Ayla Type D AT is a 5-seater LCGC (Low Cost Green Car) car which is famous for its low price, fuel economy and automatic transmission which makes it easier for drivers. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car that is affordable, easy to drive, and comfortable on busy roads. Specification: Engine: 1.0L 3 cylinder Power: 65 PS Torque: 86 Nm Transmission: 4-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 14-16 km/liter (in city) and 17-19 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags   2. Daihatsu Sigra Daihatsu Sigra is a 7-seater MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its affordable price, fuel economy and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car at an affordable price, able to accommodate many passengers, and comfortable for long trips. Specification: Engine: 1.0L 3 cylinder (D and M) / 1.2L 4 cylinder (X and R) Power: 67 PS (1.0L) / 88 PS (1.2L) Torque: 89 Nm (1.0L) / 108 Nm (1.2L) Transmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags   3. Daihatsu Rocky Daihatsu Rocky is a 5-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle) which is famous for its stylish design, reliable performance and complete features. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car with a contemporary design, strong performance and sophisticated features. Specification: Engine: 1.0L 3 cylinder Turbo (1.0R) / 1.2L 4 cylinder (1.2R) Power: 98 PS (1.0L) / 88 PS (1.2L) Torque: 140 Nm (1.0L) / 113 Nm (1.2L) Transmission: 5-speed manual or CVT automatic Fuel consumption: 16-18 km/liter (in city) and 19-21 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist, adaptive cruise control, lane departure warning, forward collision warning</string>
    <string name="daihatsu_manual">RECOMMENDATIONS FOR MANUAL DAIHATSU CARS</string>
    <string name="isi_daihatsu_manual">1. Daihatsu Xenia Daihatsu Xenia is a 7-seater MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its affordable price and fuel economy. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a spacious and comfortable cabin. Specification: Engine: 1.3L 4 cylinder Power: 97 PS Torque: 120 Nm Transmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags   2. Daihatsu Terios Daihatsu Terios is a 7-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle) which has a sporty and tough design. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with reliable performance and able to traverse various road conditions. Specification: Engine: 1.5L 4 cylinder Power: 103 PS Torque: 136 Nm Transmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic Fuel consumption: 10-12 km/liter (in city) and 13-15 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist   3. Daihatsu Ayla Type D MT Daihatsu Ayla Type D MT is a 5-seater LCGC (Low Cost Green Car) car which is famous for its low price and fuel economy. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car that is affordable and easy to drive. Specification: Engine: 1.0L 3 cylinder Power: 65 PS Torque: 86 Nm Transmission: 5-speed manual Fuel consumption: 15-17 km/liter (in city) and 18-20 km/liter (outside city) Features: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system</string>
    <string name="bagikan">Share</string>
</resources>