<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Car Recommendations</string>
    <string name="app_intro">We will help find recommendations for your car.\n\nEnter the car brand:</string>
    <string name="pilihan_merek">*brands only Toyota and Daihatsu</string>
    <string name="pilih_tipe">Select car type:</string>
    <string name="merek_mobil">Brand (Toyota or Daihatsu)</string>
    <string name="mobil_manual">Manual</string>
    <string name="mobil_matic">Matic</string>
    <string name="lihat_rekomendasi">View Recommendations</string>
    <string name="ket_rekomendasi">Recommendation results will appear below</string>

    <string name="tentang_aplikasi">About Application</string>
    <string name="copyright">This application was created to make it easier for users who are looking for car recommendations. The application will display several relevant
        car recommendations based on the brand and type of car (manual or automatic) entered by the user.\n\nCopyright © 2024 Giyats Almanfalutti.\nAll rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
    
    <string name="toyota_matic">TOYOTA MATIC CAR RECOMMENDATIONS\n</string>
    <string name="isi_toyota_matic">1. Toyota Avanza\nThe Toyota Avanza is a 7-seater MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its affordable price, fuel economy
        and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car at an affordable price, able to accommodate many passengers, and comfortable for long
        trips.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.3L 4 cylinder and 1.5L 4 cylinder\nPower: 98 PS (1.3L) and 106 PS (1.5L)\nTorque: 12.4 Nm (1.3L) and 14.1 Nm (1.5L)\nTransmission:
        5-speed manual and CVT automatic\nFuel consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in the city) and 16-18 km / liter (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power window, power
        steering, audio system, ABS, airbag, electronic parking brake\n\n 2. Toyota Kijang Innova\nThe Toyota Kijang Innova is an MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) 7 -seater which
        is famous for its elegant design, reliable performance and comfortable interior. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design,
        strong performance and a spacious cabin.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 2.0L 4 cylinder and 2.4L 4 cylinder\nPower: 139 PS (2.0L) and 149 PS (2.4L)\nTorque: 183 Nm
        (2.0L) and 239 Nm (2.4L)\nTransmission: 5-speed manual and 6-speed automatic\nFuel consumption: 10-12 km/liter (in the city) and 13-15 km/liter
        (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist, panoramic sunroof\n\n 3.
        Toyota Fortuner\nToyota Fortuner is an SUV ( Sport Utility Vehicle) 7-seater which is famous for its dashing design, reliable performance and complete features.
        This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance and sophisticated features.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 2.4L 4
        cylinder and 2.8L 4 cylinder\nPower: 149 PS (2.4L) and 204 PS (2.8L)\nTorque: 400 Nm (2.4L) and 420 Nm (2.8L)\nTransmission: 6-speed manual and 6-speed automatic\nFuel
        consumption: 9-11 km/liter (in city) and 12-14 km/liter (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking
        brake, hill start assist, adaptive cruise control, lane departure warning, forward collision warning</string>

    <string name="toyota_manual">TOYOTA MANUAL CAR RECOMMENDATIONS\n</string>
    <string name="isi_toyota_manual">1. Toyota Corolla\nThe Toyota Corolla is a sedan that is famous for its elegant design, reliable performance and comfortable interior. This
        car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance and a spacious cabin.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.8L 4 cylinder\nPower:
        140 PS\nTorque: 171 Nm\nTransmission: 6-speed manual or Automatic CVT\nFuel consumption: 12-14 km/liter (in city) and 15-17 km/liter (outside city)\nFeatures: AC,
        power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist\n\n 2. Toyota Yaris\nThe Toyota Yaris is a hatchback car that is
        famous for its sporty design, reliable performance and complete features. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car with a contemporary design, strong
        performance and sophisticated features.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.5L 4 cylinder\nPower: 107 PS\nTorque: 140 Nm\nTransmission: 5-speed manual or Automatic CVT\nFuel
        consumption: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city)\nFeatures: AC, power window, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbag, electronic parking brake,
        hill start assist, paddle shift\n\n 3. Toyota Rush\nToyota Rush is a 7-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle) which is famous for its sporty design, reliable performance
        and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a stylish design, strong performance, and a cabin that can accommodate many passengers.
        \nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.5L 4 cylinder\nPower: 104 PS\nTorque: 138 Nm\nTransmission: Manual 5-speed or 4-speed automatic\nFuel consumption: 10-12 km/liter
        (in the city) and 13-15 km/liter (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags , electronic parking brake, hill start
        assist</string>

    <string name="daihatsu_matic">DAIHATSU MATIC CAR RECOMMENDATIONS\n</string>
    <string name="isi_daihatsu_matic">1. Daihatsu Ayla Type D AT\nDaihatsu Ayla Type D AT is a 5-seater LCGC (Low Cost Green Car) car which is famous for its low price, fuel
        economy and automatic transmission which makes it easier for drivers. This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car that is affordable, easy to drive and
        comfortable on busy roads.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.0L 3 cylinder\nPower: 65 PS\nTorque: 86 Nm\nTransmission: 4-speed automatic\n nFuel consumption: 14-16 km/liter
        (in city) and 17-19 km/liter (outside city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags\n\n 2. Daihatsu Sigra\nDaihatsu Sigra is a 7-seater
        MPV (Multi-Purpose Vehicle) car which is famous for its affordable price, fuel economy and spacious cabin. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car at
        an affordable price, able to accommodate many passengers, and comfortable for long trips.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.0L 3 cylinders (D and M) / 1.2L 4 cylinders
        (X and R)\\ nPower: 67 PS (1.0L) / 88 PS (1.2L)\nTorque: 89 Nm (1.0L) / 108 Nm (1.2L)\nTransmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic\nFuel consumption: 13-15
        km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter (outside city)\nFeatures: AC, power window, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbag\n\n 3. Daihatsu Rocky\nDaihatsu Rocky is
        an SUV ( Sport Utility Vehicle) 5-seater which is famous for its stylish design, reliable performance and complete features. This car is suitable for drivers who want
        to have a car with a contemporary design, strong performance and sophisticated features.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.0L 3 cylinder Turbo (1.0R) / 1.2L 4 cylinder
        (1.2R)\nPower: 98 PS (1.0L) / 88 PS (1.2L)\nTorque: 140 Nm (1.0L) / 113 Nm (1.2L)\nTransmission: 5-speed manual or CVT automatic\nFuel consumption: 16-18 km/liter
        (in city) and 19-21 km/liter (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake, hill start assist,
        adaptive cruise control, lane departure warning, forward collision warning</string>

    <string name="daihatsu_manual">DAIHATSU MANUAL CAR RECOMMENDATIONS\n</string>
    <string name="isi_daihatsu_manual">1. Daihatsu Xenia\nDaihatsu This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with a spacious and comfortable cabin.\nSpecifications:\nEngine:
        1.3L 4 cylinder\nPower: 97 PS\nTorque: 120 Nm\nTransmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic\nConsumption Fuel: 13-15 km/liter (in city) and 16-18 km/liter
        (outside city)\nFeatures: AC, power window, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbag\n\n 2. Daihatsu Terios\nDaihatsu Terios is a 7-seater SUV (Sport Utility Vehicle)
        which has a sporty and tough design. This car is suitable for families who want to have a car with reliable performance and is able to overcome various road
        conditions.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.5L 4 cylinder\nPower: 103 PS\nTorque: 136 Nm\nTransmission: 5-speed manual or 4-speed automatic -acceleration\nFuel consumption:
        10-12 km/liter (in the city) and 13-15 km/liter (outside the city)\nFeatures: AC, power windows, power steering, audio system, ABS, airbags, electronic parking brake,
        hill start assist\n\n 3. Daihatsu Ayla Type D MT\nDaihatsu Ayla Type D MT is a 5-seater LCGC (Low Cost Green Car) car which is famous for its low price and fuel economy.
        This car is suitable for drivers who want to have a car at an affordable price and easy to drive.\nSpecifications:\nEngine: 1.0L 3 cylinder\nPower: 65 PS\nTorque:
        86 Nm\nTransmission: 5-speed manual\nFuel consumption: 15-17 km/liter (in city) and 18-20 km/liter (outside city)\nFeatures: AC, power window, power steering, audio
        system</string>

    <string name="bagikan">Share</string>

    <string name="input_error">------ INVALID INPUT! ------</string>

</resources>